we are relaxed oh man go peace
all right what it city what a thing can
we take a second to shill for vocables
products oh this brings back all good
old memories of the road trip road trip
Emmys I remember getting really good
angles here because you can see your
face with impaired - I perfected this so
sadly Oh pilot don't see very well right
now this doesn't HDR yo that guy 49 is
now banned topic if he says it again bad
I don't know a fortnight even is playing
Age of Empires though right that's right
that's good that's good it happen 2018 ,
ski trip yeah it is the first of the you
know potentially more 2018 ski trips
it's great it's the only official
combination ski trip this is the first
ever car company trip no the subtitle
car where's too
singing comity Anya so you coming you
know we I don't know where our Dooley on
technology went to the developers we got
we got a single you right now
baby
[Music]
drive
we got away for the camera crew project
let us help you with your merch George
sure yo yeah what shall I do
chill for the merch bros tell your
friends all right so big announcement to
make
if you're telling the big announcement
no just created and said I think you
guys know what's up you guys will find
exactly if you know what's up you'll
know what's up and if not it's really no
big deal
no biggie that's right that's right
biggie would be happy but no big this is
the softest
you can't convey to your radio stations
up here in town Chelsea either no we've
got 55 people we got to give him
something something entertaining I don't
know we should do more in the commas key
Jim you guys ever go skiing and it's
been like a long day and now it's like
we're like way later than you want to so
this is Scobie Saturday yeah their
bounty on the 2018 Accord they brought
in
with the oneplus good enough that is
what those camera good enough to handle
all tasks and situations well it's made
by soap so you know you don't know
people thank you Melo's
if there's any questions I am reading
him I'm reading all the questions I got
I think
be like what you're doing and would like
to work
that's great okay and handle extreme
weather conditions heavy fog rain at
night no definitely not
they can't even handle this this is
extreme Sun yeah is the dynamic the deal
you guys running a grey panda yeah
heading towards our out of Tahoe still
in Tahoe and for the next day yeah we're
headed back to the place that we were
staying in Tahoe
benches couches they're all the same no
but you know we're gonna do that guys we
can flip monopolies
like you get really competitive what
yeah I love a novel and the such thing
as competitive Wally was designed to
show the negative effects of the
monopoly rate no monopoly was designed
to show the glory of capitalism well
extreme battery with a new camera person
yeah well there's just me like a few
people reached out but my girlfriend
said handoff will she doesn't believe
she doesn't believe there in utica
maverick merchandise I know sorry my app
crash is there a bounty 422 being
extreme weather conditions two days now
unfortunately our rav4 is not yet modded
did you stop and go so I'm gonna have to
drive here see look comic cancelled
we're working on the mod it's like the
engine computer in his car is half
modded yeah look how good that focus is
what
it's in focus
let's go don't you feel like it's a
common thing heard around Thomas
traffic how's the stop sign I think the
resort is closed and there's not that
many directions to go in Tahoe so this
has the stop but yes coming good thank
you you can answer to here
actually we probably route of stock they
were to left yesterday great pandas are
fairly exclusive product but white
pandas there's many many of many very
cute boxes actually I'm excited for the
gray panda unboxing videos you guys are
gonna make we worked really hard on it
you guys still have any fuel assembly
ons that's okay they're all together
you don't ship out real fast be getting
the on ships out within three days
let's try to stop and go home
does his girlfriend believe now does
your girlfriend believe us
so we have our destination here in ways
says be home at 16 minutes Oh Missy my
[Music]
periscope accessible you know actually
they kick you out of poker table in
Vegas we all speak English language
tables it's the announcement that great
pandas are supported and working sure
yeah oh yeah yeah that's funny I mean
yeah I supported like the new people
said yeah she believes us fabulous
the Newport D does work with dance
well guys we used Schiffer to find our
parked car to that our car was parked I
mean shiver
yeah
and snow scooters oh no no no it's not
gonna work this is the snow it's the
same promise course understand hey does
the yen have freaking alerts for older
cars that don't have the tech ie camera
based alert yeah
no not camera basis to get it radar
it was the clown motel here last night I
want to show them a beautiful view of
the water but I just missed it
unfortunately
sorry folks I thought that's a ten
vacancy if it actually says no vacancy
the scope is know what those to do in
Tahoe tonight yeah what do you scope
know well actually last something about
a scope it was it was great but you know
company ski trips confidence for company
but you got you guys are here to see the
come to ski trip we got to drive all the
way back
low energy powers I know are they still
people it's like 36 but they're dropping
new people coming on joining us coping
right now so this isn't else copy let's
go be Saturday so let's go be Sunday I
was ranting about the car companies this
morning but you know after a long tired
day of stuff no I'm slack but after a
long tired day of physical exercise you
just don't like feel like rant about you
anymore
can we add radar no cars yet no but like
serious if you duct-tape a traitor to a
car and connected to a neon duct tape to
the front common like the original
didn't duct taping some radars to our
car in the very beginning
what else to Vegas sketchy pedal
interceptor
I was why did I talk about last night
that's a beach looks like it it's so
pleasant